Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
Soon after arriving at the underwater temple in search of the magic stone,
the Black Bulls were roped into High Priest Jifso's game, a high-stakes temple battle royale.
All my temple mages are more powerful than intermediate-class magic knights.
And they're out there fighting a bunch of juniors?
They're losing? That's impossible!
It's gonna take more than a few drops of water to scare me off.
Magna and Luck face the same opponent, vying for the chance to defeat him.
First come, first serve! Sorry!
Lightning magic! Thunderbolt destruction!
Seven!
Well, well, aren't you a spunky little fellow?
I'll have you know my son is the most powerful mage in the underwater temple.
He's got so much power, like a tidal wave. This guy is the strongest one here.
I'll take you both on at once. I'm not interested in tormenting you any further.
What a creation magic! Poseidon's hammer!
You're not gonna be ending anything!
Yeah, I'm nowhere near done playing with you!
The game was interrupted by the arrival of Vedo, a top member of the Eye of the Midnight Sun.
Well, it looks like you folks are having quite a get-together.
How about you guys let me in the mix?
Thanks to my friends.
And now, everyone hi friends.
Woah
I'm falling down
I'm not gonna be any longer
Bye-bye, yeah
Just move it back
Byっかり抱きしめ
汗しなするへ
Just move it back
光灯して
真っ暗な音色へ
Just move it back
La la la la la la la
La-la la la la la la la
くど迷えのキーパ落ち完了
invertが明iezある
oh wow, the full moon looks so gorgeous
Wherever Asta is, I wonder if he's looking up at the same moon right now.
Silly mimosa.
I guess I must have nodded off for a bit.
Ha! Barely enough for a decent warm-up. That was like fighting a bunch of puny mice. Time to go.
Sir!
They may not have been expecting an attack, but that's still a lot of top-ranked mages.
It shouldn't have been possible for one guy to take them all out in a matter of minutes.
These are the people we trust to protect the kingdom. How could this happen?
One thing's sure. That was no human. That thing was... a beast.
What's this guy think he's doing crashing our battle? And why is he so hairy?
Yeah, no fair. Shark Head totally belonged to me.
Maybe it's okay, though. This guy's got more magic power than Captain Yami.
You made it through the ocean currents and forced your way into the underwater temple.
Your magic must be formidable indeed.
Oh. I see you can still move.
Well, that hurt.
You and your buddies there sure don't look like magic knights.
I know why they're here, but what do you people want with the underwater temple?
The same thing that they do. We're here for the magic stone, too.
Are you? Well, that's too bad. We can't simply hand it over, you know.
I'm sure. I wouldn't want it to be that effortless anyway.
I'd much rather plunge you all into despair, destroy this place, and take the stone myself!
You what?
The rest of you, go. Spread out through the temple.
Sir.
It's rude to drop in uninvited like this. I'm afraid I'll have to ask you to leave, please.
Silence, peon!
You really do need to work on your manners.
It will take far more powerful magic than you possess to make me leave this place without that stone.
Oh dear. You clearly don't understand who you're dealing with.
Of all the underwater temples' mages, I am the strongest by far.
Enough chit-chat! We can let our magic do the talking.
Very well. Mine has plenty to say.
Water creation magic! Now, Poseidon's Hammer!
No!
That little hammer spell is no match for my rhinoceros armor.
There's not a scratch on him.
Still not a bad try for a temple mouse. You've earned a prize.
A prize?
That's right. A swift death!
In nature, the mighty beasts get to devour their prey as a reward for their strength,
while the pathetic vermin like you only get destruction and despair!
My beast magic, bear claws!
Do you understand the situation? You see the overwhelming difference in our power? You are insects. I shall not allow you to retain even a shred of hope!
No. That shouldn't have been possible.
Jiho is the strongest that we have. He was beaten so easily. I've never seen such power. And I've seen much in my time.
Listen, old man. Playtime's over now. Get me out there to my people and do it fast.
This must be serious if you're rattled. Who is he? He looks more like a beast than a man.
He's a high-ranking member of the group I told you about, the Eye of the Midnight Sun.
Eye of the Midnight Sun?
There's no time to explain. Just get me out of here, alright?
I'm sorry, Captain. I'm afraid that won't be possible. We are stuck in here.
We can't leave until the game is finished. And I can't break the spell, either. That's the way it is. We'll just have to wait and see.
Is that so?
What are you...
Guess I'll just have to let myself out.
Huh?
Dark magic! Light-lit SLAT!
Let's SLAT!
Huh?
Hey! What happened to my temple?
Damn. What is this?
Spatial magic. Different dimension sphere.
Once somebody has been ensnared by my spatial magic, they have no hope of escaping unless I decide to release them from its hold.
Dark swordsmen from a foreign land.
Yes, that's right. I can tell you're here by the mana.
Watch from the sidelines a little longer. You're going to be my main dish.
You'll be steeped in delicious despair from having seen the deaths of all your friends.
We must do something to stop this beast. Or else the temple is done for.
Alright, geezer.
What is it?
We can't get in there, but can we still talk to him?
Well, yes. We can.
But how will that help them?
Uh, testing, one, two, test, test.
Oh my gosh. That's Captain Yami!
Alright, you morons. Listen up!
Hey, Captain! I actually beat one of them!
A nasty character just crashed the party.
He's one of the Midnight Sun's high-ranked members. Real wild-looking SOB who's as strong as a magic knight captain.
He's here?
Plus, he's got four meetings with him.
Does he need another helping plus?
But some things have come up so I can't get to him.
Huh? What things exactly?
You black kids are going to have to handle it.
You've got to be kidding me!
Now look. It's time to get serious. Push past your limits.
Die and I'll kill you. No worry now.
Great. We're basically doomed.
When I proposed this game of mine, I had no idea it would turn out to be so exhilarating.
And now here we are, with the fate of the underwater temple hanging in the balance.
Time for a rule change!
Knights and mages!
In order to win the game, you must defeat Team Eye of the Midnight Sun.
All those who contribute to this victory will have their wishes granted.
Insofar as my authority is the high priest of this temple of ours!
We have to fight that monster!
Yeah, he's scary.
So what?
That's exactly what makes a battle worth fighting!
I can do this!
I can take him down!
Asta.
I guess this means that our fight is on hold.
Guess so.
Alright, let's go!
Too easy.
Now, who's going to be my next prey?
Where you going?
Think you can move on to the next fight just like that?
Get back here.
We're not dead yet.
Captain Yami gave us our marching orders.
And if our captain says to take you down, that's what we're gonna do.
You got that?
We're not done yet!
We won't be broken!
Excellent.
I shall enjoy bringing you despair that much more.
The longer the hunt continues, the greater the anticipation of the kill becomes.
I'm glad we're still going.
But how are we gonna fight a monster like that?
If he lands one more square hit on us, we're toast!
Hey, big guy!
Throw that last attack spell at us again, will ya?
Yeah, the super-fast one!
Has all that lightning finally fried his brain?
We barely survived that one the first time!
How are we supposed to live to a second round?
Well, well.
We've got a feisty one.
I'm glad we're still going.
But how are we gonna fight a monster like that?
If he lands one more square hit on us, we're toast!
Hey, big guy!
Throw that last attack spell at us again, will ya?
Yeah, the super-fast one!
Has all that lightning finally fried his brain?
We barely survived that one the first time!
How are we supposed to live to a second round?
Well, well.
We've got a feisty one.
Delicious.
Then I'll continue feeding you despair.
Until you choke!
You leave yourself open for just a second.
I thought I saw that before.
And you're fast enough to take advantage of it.
You have keen perception and incredible speed, I'll grant you that.
Oh man, my thunderbolt destruction didn't have any effect on him at all!
I can play with you a while longer!
He's all over the place!
He's all over the place.
Huh?
Heh!
Heh heh!
Ha ha ha!
That crazy battle freak.
Damn him.
It's Magna, right?
You've got some weird-looking hair.
What?
I'm Luck. Nice to meet you.
Oh, this guy?
I think he's that smiling maniac they call Luck the Cheery Berserker.
Looks like I'm gonna have to show him what's what.
Yeah, nice to meet you too, you jerk.
Oh, hey! That's a funny face!
You've been messing around and annoying the crap out of me ever since the very first day you joined the squad.
Everyone knows you've got more than your share of personality issues.
Hot, hot, hot, hot, hot, hot, hot, hot.
And half the time on missions, you're more trouble than you're worth.
Ha!
Huh?
That's the Krappling man the typhoon!
Still, your battle sense?
I gotta give it to you there.
And ever since that dungeon mission, you've only been getting stronger.
You're reckless, immature, and insane.
I hate to admit it, but damn it, you're my best friend.
Hmm.
That's it.
You better not even think about leaving me behind, you jerk!
Flame creation magic!
Grand slam!
Yeah, right out of the park!
Ha-ha!
Hey, nice one, Magna!
Here, let me help!
When we first met, I didn't take you seriously.
A commoner, huh?
Boring.
But something told me that behind the weird-looking hair, there was somebody truly dangerous and entertaining.
I kept messing with you so I could meet that, Magna.
Hey, thanks for the blonde! It was tasty!
Just because that's the last thing you'll ever eat!
You always come right back at me with everything you've got.
You never hold anything back.
And now, after all this time, I finally realized you were the first friend I ever made.
Hey, Magna!
You can do better than that, can't ya?
Shut up!
That wasn't a bad catch, Fireball Freak.
What? Who are you calling a freak? Now get off me, Lightning Boy!
If you two are done playing, can we finish this?
That's it! Let's kick this guy's ass!
Sure sounds good to me! We're ready whenever you are!
Ha-ha.
This way!
How do you know where to go when you can't sense mana?
I can't sense mana, but I can sense Ki!
Ki!
Ki? Anyway, you're right. I sense magic power up ahead.
And there's a tremendous amount of it, too.
I never felt anything like this before.
I agree with you that this is a battle that's worth fighting!
Hey, I was trying to read your Ki earlier.
It was almost impossible to pin you down.
How do you do that?
Oh, well, my dancing actually puts me into a kind of trance,
which is a really big help when it comes to fighting.
How does it work?
My body just sort of moves without any conscious thought on my part.
That makes it hard for my opponent to predict what I'll do.
Okay, I get it. That's really cool!
A trance!
What you doing?
Putting myself in a trance.
Ha-ha.
Whoa! I can see the magic up ahead clearly now.
Flame mixed with lightning, and they're doing battle!
Flame and lightning, huh?
That means Magna and Luck are up there.
And as for the massive power they're fighting,
what is this?
It's like hundreds of wild animals snarling and running crazy.
That's Feno's magic!
Wait, how the heck can you pick up on all that?
Our kind are particularly skilled at reading magic and the different forms it can take.
But if that's what we're up against, then I'm worried.
It's fine.
Those two may be a little bit on the crazy side,
but you can always count on them when things start to get tough.
We'll get out of this alive!
That hurts.
Now are you beginning to understand?
Weak animals will be devoured.
Their lot in life is to despair.
But you shut up!
The last thing I'm feeling right now is despair.
That's right.
We can't give up.
No way.
If we quit that easily, then we wouldn't deserve to be his superiors anymore.
Not yet.
He's right.
Fighting normally, we wouldn't stand a chance against this guy.
Not yet.
There it is.
That opening is split second after his attack.
Now!
We won't give up.
We're going to fight with everything we've got.
A simultaneous attack at point-blank range and thrive on my weak point.
Not yet.
A
All right.
You got this.
So much mana.
This power is incredible.
Combo spell.
꿈 of lightning exploding cannon.
Magna, look, we're coming! Are you okay?
Foyいても消えない強い不安
For hours, lately I've been crying for hours, baby
I wish you were here
君がくれたall those letters
読み返すたびに
The pain's gone
ひとりじゃない
Cause we're a perfect dance floor
離ればなれでも
繋がるBelieve in you
いつもそばに感じているから
Bless out of me
And I'll go before you
君に行く
You know you're not alone
Cause we're a perfect dance floor
離ればなれでも
繋がるBelieve in me
いつもそばに
私がいるから
Fly out of me
And I'll go before you
君に行く
CLOVERCLIPS
CRACKLING MAGNA TYPHOON
Hey everyone
How's it going?
Less your excitement people
Kick it up a nut or two already
Today we're going to teach you a fun and easy way
To pull off a crackling magna typhoon
In the comfort of your own home
First get a length of lightning rope ready like so
Are you kidding?
Then you wrap it around your very own magna
Stopping me!
Right!
Now you try whipping up a rope magna
I can't do that!
You're doing great
We're almost done
Once the rope's nice and tight
Give him a push to get him spinning
Here we go!
Here you have it folks
A crackling magna typhoon
So easy anyone can do it
No you idiot
You're the only one who can do it!
Bye for now!
No matter how tough the enemy may be
I'm not giving up
Not ever
I'm a black bull
We all are!
Black Clover page 45
The guy who doesn't know when to quit
That's right
My magic is never giving up!